[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my little brother,
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mummy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
PEPPA:
School Camp.
NARRATOR: Peppa and her friends
are going on a school camp.
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
Madame Gazelle,
I don't feel very well.
The bus is very bumpy.
NARRATOR: Oh, dear, Pedro Pony
is feeling a bit travel sick.
Poor Pedro.
Come and sit in the front
with me.
[GIGGLES]
There. Is that better?
A little bit.
Madame Gazelle.
Oh.
Do you feel sick too, Zoe?
I might feel sick later.
Can I sit at the front
just in case?
[SNORTS]
Can I sit at the front too?
ALL:
And me.
Ho, ho. I'm sorry, children,
you can't all sit
at the front.
ALL:
Oh.
Never mind.
We're at the campsite now.
ALL:
Hooray!
[ALL LAUGHING]
Happy camping, everyone.
ALL:
Bye-bye!
Ho, ho.
This is our campsite.
Breathe in the wonderful
fresh air, children.
[INHALES DEEPLY
THEN EXHALES AUDIBLY]
[ALL INHALE DEEPLY
THEN EXHALE AUDIBLY]
Excellent breathing.
Now let's put up our tents.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her friends
are putting up their tents.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Children,
you must each find a partner
to share your tent.
Suzy, shall we share a tent?
[BAAS]
I said I'd share with Zoe.
Oh. Sorry, Suzy.
I said I'd share
with Rebecca.
Rebecca,
you said you'd share with me.
Oh, yes.
[BAAS]
Emily, who are you going
to share
a tent with?
Um...
Zoe.
Okay.
Good.
Now you can share with me.
Okay.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Now I need sticks
to make a campfire.
We'll get sticks.
But me and Pedro
want to get sticks.
Ho, ho.
You can all collect sticks.
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her friends collect
sticks for the campfire.
Wonderful.
[HOOTING]
NARRATOR:
It is nighttime.
Peppa and her friends are
sitting around the campfire.
Children,
let's all sing a song.
ALL: Yes!
"The Bing Bong Song,"
please.
Oh, I'm not sure.
ALL:
Please, Madame Gazelle.
Sing "The Bing Bong Song."
All right.
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ We're playing a tune
And we're singing a song ♪
♪ With a bing and a bong
And a bing ♪
♪ Bong bing boo ♪
♪ Bing bong bing ♪
♪ Bing bong
Bingley bungley boo ♪
♪ Bong bing boo ♪
♪ Bing bong bing ♪
♪ Bing bong
Bingley bungley boo ♪
[ALL LAUGHING]
Ho, ho.
Now, children, time for bed.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Good night, children.
ALL:
Goodnight, Madame Gazelle.
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and Suzy
are in their sleeping bags.
I've got a torch.
Me too.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Attention, children.
No more giggling, please.
[HOOTING]
What was that funny noise?
I don't know.
[HOOTING CONTINUES]
There it is again.
Suzy, where are you going?
Madame Gazelle.
I'm a bit scared.
Oh,
would you like to come in?
Yes, please.
Madame Gazelle.
I think
I'm a bit scared too.
Can I come in, please?
Of course.
[GIGGLES]
I think
I might be scared later.
I might be scared later too.
BOTH:
And me.
Come in, everyone.
[ALL LAUGHING]
PEPPA: Can we have
"The Bing Bong Song," please?
MADAME GAZELLE:
All right.
♪ We're playing a tune ♪
♪ And we're singing a song ♪
♪ With a bing and a bong
and a bing ♪♪
PEPPA:
Captain Daddy Pig.
NARRATOR: Peppa and her family
are borrowing Grandpa's boat
for the day.
[SNORTS]
Remember, Daddy Pig,
push the lever forward
to go forward.
Aye, aye, Grandpa Pig.
Forward.
And back to go back.
And back. Simple.
And please
look after my boat.
I've just had it painted.
Oh, Grandpa Pig,
what an old fusspot you are.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Are my crew ready?
ALL:
Yes, Captain Daddy Pig.
Then let's go.
NARRATOR: Oh,
the boat is moving backwards.
Aah!
Watch out for the bridge.
Oops.
Oh, that was close.
Bye-bye.
ALL:
Have a lovely time.
[SNORTS]
I hope my boat comes back
in one piece.
Stop worrying.
It will be fine.
[♪♪♪]
Peppa, ring the bell.
Aye, aye, Captain Daddy.
[BELL RINGING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SNORTS]
I'm a bit hungry.
So am I.
Grandpa's left us a picnic,
in the galley.
What's a galley?
A galley
is a boat's little kitchen.
Follow me.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
are going inside the boat.
BOTH: Wow.
What a tiny little kitchen.
[SNORTS]
Where's the picnic?
The obvious place
would be here.
[DADDY PIG GRUNTS
THEN PEPPA GIGGLES]
That's not a picnic.
Then it must be here.
And that's not a picnic.
This kitchen has everything
in the wrong place.
Wow, a TV.
[CAR ENGINES WHIRRING]
NARRATOR: Daddy Pig
cannot find the picnic.
It's impossible.
[SNORTS]
If this was my kitchen,
the picnic would be here.
Oh. Well done, Peppa.
NARRATOR:
Peppa has found the picnic.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Delicious.
[DUCKS QUACKING]
Oh, it's the ducks.
[QUACKS]
Hello, Mrs. Duck.
Would you like some bread?
[DUCKS QUACKING]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
love feeding bread
to ducks.
[DUCKS QUACKING]
Look out. Long reeds ahead.
Don't worry, Grandpa's boat
will easily go through them.
[ENGINE CREAKING]
Are we stuck?
No. We can reverse.
Now, are we stuck?
Yes.
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear, Grandpa's boat
is stuck in the reeds.
I'll just give it
a little push.
Do be careful, Daddy Pig.
I know what I'm doing.
When I say "Go,"
start the engine.
ALL:
Aye, aye, Captain Daddy Pig.
Go.
[ENGINE STARTS
THEN DADDY PIG GRUNTS]
NARRATOR: Daddy Pig has pushed
the boat out of the reeds.
ALL:
Hooray!
[SNORTS]
Quick, Daddy!
Jump back on the boat!
[PANTING]
NARRATOR: Oh, no,
Daddy Pig is being left behind.
Swim faster, Daddy.
Stop the engine.
What's he saying?
[MUFFLED]
Stop the engine.
Daddy says,
"Stop the engine."
Oh.
[PANTING]
MUMMY PIG:
Are you okay, Daddy Pig?
Yes, I'm fine.
But let's head for home
before we have
any more adventures.
ALL:
Aye, aye, Captain Daddy Pig.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
They've been gone for ages.
I hope my boat's all right.
[BELL RINGING]
Look, there they are.
ALL: Hello.
BOTH: Ahoy there.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
I'll just park the boat.
[LAUGHS]
You park a car,
but you moor a boat.
I'll show you.
NARRATOR: Grandpa Pig
is going to moor the boat.
[SNORTS]
The secret of mooring
is to do it carefully.
Mind the bridge.
What?
ALL:
Look behind you.
Aah!
[♪♪♪]
Oh.
I didn't mean to do that.
Grandpa has broken his boat.
Never mind, Grandpa.
You can have lots of fun
mending it.
It is true
that I love mending things.
Can I help mend the boat,
Grandpa?
Ho, ho.
Of course you can, Peppa.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
PEPPA:
The Power Cut.
NARRATOR: It is evening.
[ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Peppa and George
are in the sitting room,
dancing
to their favorite song.
Daddy Pig is in the hallway
vacuuming the carpet.
And Mummy Pig
is in her study
doing important work
on her computer.
Oh.
[MUSIC STOPS]
Mommy, Daddy,
it's gone all dark
and the music is broken.
And my vacuum won't work.
And my computer
has switched off.
BOTH: Ooh.
NARRATOR: Mummy Pig
tries the light switch,
but the lights
do not come on.
It must be a power cut.
[SNORTS]
What's a power cut?
A power cut
is when there is no electricity.
What's electric-kity?
Electricity
is what makes everything
in our house work.
Will the electric-kity
come back again?
Yes.
[SNORTS]
But in the meantime,
we need to find a torch.
I think there's a torch
in the cellar.
Okay, I'll go and get it.
Will you be okay, Daddy?
Ho, ho, I'll be fine.
I can see very well
in the dark.
[CLANGING AND HONKING]
Who put that there?
Oh.
Daddy, are you okay?
DADDY PIG: Yes,
it's just a bit dark down here.
[CLANGING AND CRASHING]
Oh, I've just remembered.
I think the torch
is in the kitchen.
[PEPPA AND GEORGE GIGGLING]
Ah-ha.
NARRATOR:
Mummy Pig has found the torch.
Can I hold the torch, Mummy?
Okay.
[GIGGLES]
George.
Look at me.
NARRATOR:
Peppa is making a funny face.
[CRYING]
Don't worry, George,
it's only Peppa.
[ALL LAUGH]
Oh, we'd better tell Daddy
we found the torch.
[OBJECTS CLANGING]
NARRATOR:
Daddy is still in the cellar,
looking for the torch.
I'm sure it's here
somewhere.
PEPPA:
Daddy, we found the torch.
Luckily, it was in the kitchen
all the time.
What a stroke of luck.
[LAUGHS]
[SNORTS]
Now we just have to wait
until the electricity
comes back.
How long will that be
exactly?
Um, I would say,
exactly a long time.
BOTH:
Oh.
But George and I
want to do some dancing.
[SNORTS]
I know what we can do.
We can watch
some television.
Oh, it won't go on.
[MUMMY PIG AND DADDY PIG
LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
The TV needs electricity too.
Does it?
BOTH: Yes.
Oh.
Now what are we going to do?
In the olden days,
when there was no television,
children would have to make up
their own games.
Hm. I know.
[SNORTS]
I need a cardboard box.
NARRATOR:
What is Peppa doing?
[SNORTS]
Mommy, will you cut a hole
in this box for me?
What for?
You'll see.
NARRATOR:
Mummy Pig is cutting a hole
in the cardboard box.
There you are, Peppa.
Thank you.
Now, you all have
to sit down there.
And, George, you have to point
this torch at me.
[SNORTS]
[GIGGLING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Welcome to Peppa Pig News
with me, Peppa Pig.
[ALL LAUGH]
NARRATOR: Peppa has made
her own television.
[SNORTS]
Today, the whole world
stopped working
when there was a power cut,
and all the electric-kity
was lost.
[ALL LAUGH]
Very good, Peppa.
Daddy Pig says
that the electric-kity
won't be back
for a long, long time.
ALL: Oh.
NARRATOR:
The electricity is back.
ALL: Hooray!
Shush, I haven't finished yet.
[SNORTS]
Switch the lights off.
Okay, Peppa.
Good.
Ahem.
I have
some very important news.
The queen has just found
some more electric-kity,
and says that everyone
can now be happy again.
Very good, Peppa.
ALL:
Hooray!
Let's dance.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
AND PEPPA LAUGHING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR: Peppa quite enjoyed
the power cut,
but she's happy
the electricity is back again.
PEPPA:
Bouncy Ball.
[♪♪♪]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR: Peppa and George
are going to play
in the garden
with their ball.
Whee!
NARRATOR:
George throws the ball
as high as he can
and catches it.
[GIGGLES]
[SNORTS]
I can do that too.
Whee!
Oh.
NARRATOR:
Peppa has missed the ball.
[GIGGLES]
This is a silly game.
[BICYCLE BELL RINGING]
[BAAS]
NARRATOR:
Here is Peppa's best friend,
Suzy Sheep.
Suzy has two
tennis rackets.
Hello, Peppa.
[SNORTS]
Hello, Suzy.
Let's play tennis.
Yes, that sounds fun.
[SNORTS]
To you, Suzy.
Oh.
NARRATOR:
Suzy has missed the ball.
[GIGGLES]
Oh.
NARRATOR:
Peppa has missed the ball.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR: Peppa and Suzy
like playing tennis,
but George feels
a bit left out.
[CRYING]
Oh. Sorry, George.
You can't play tennis.
We only have two rackets.
[SOBS]
I know.
George can be the ball boy.
Yes. It's a very important job.
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR: George is going
to be the ball boy.
He has to collect the ball
when it is hit too far.
To you, Suzy.
Oh, missed it.
BOTH:
Ball boy.
[GEORGE SNORTS THEN GIGGLES]
[PANTING]
Thank you, ball boy.
Oh.
BOTH:
Ball boy.
[GEORGE PANTING]
Thank you, ball boy.
BOTH:
Ball boy.
[CRYING]
NARRATOR: Oh, dear.
George doesn't like this game.
[BICYCLE BELLS RINGING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Here are Danny Dog,
Pedro Pony, Candy Cat,
Rebecca Rabbit,
and Richard Rabbit.
Hello, everyone.
ALL: Hello.
[SNORTS]
We're playing tennis.
Can we play too?
But there aren't
enough racquets.
ALL: Oh.
Let's play something else.
[BARKS]
Let's play football.
ALL:
Yes, football.
[SNORTS]
Girls against boys.
[ALL LAUGHING]
We each need a goalkeeper.
Me, me.
NARRATOR:
Pedro Pony and Rebecca Rabbit
will be the goalkeepers.
We'll start.
[GIGGLES]
[SQUEAKING THEN GIGGLING]
BOTH:
Goal!
NARRATOR: Richard Rabbit
has scored a goal.
The boys are winning.
[BOTH LAUGH]
That's not fair.
We weren't ready.
[GIGGLES]
Hey, that's cheating.
You can't hold the ball.
Yes, I can,
I'm the goalkeeper.
ALL:
Go, Rebecca, go!
Oof.
Goal.
ALL GIRLS:
Hooray!
The goal is not allowed.
ALL:
Yes, it is.
No, it isn't.
ALL:
Yes, it is.
What a lot of noise.
Daddy,
the boys are cheating.
No, the girls are cheating.
It sounds like
you need a referee.
What's a referee?
It's someone who makes sure
that everyone plays fair.
ALL:
I'll be the referee! Me, me, me!
Stop, stop!
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
I'll be the referee.
[SNORTS]
The next team to get a goal
will win the game.
ALL: Hooray!
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
[SNORTS]
Where's the ball?
[BOTH GIGGLING]
Quick, score a goal.
Stop them.
[GIGGLING CONTINUES]
Oof.
Goal!
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
Richard Rabbit
has scored a goal.
ALL: Hooray!
The boys win.
ALL: Oh.
Football is a silly game.
Just a moment.
The boys scored
in their own goal.
That means the girls win.
Really?
ALL:
Hooray!
Football is a great game.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING AND SNORTING]
PEPPA:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING AND GIGGLING]